<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Deepmind on Stanford RL Forum</title>
    <link>https://97hongjun.github.io/categories/deepmind/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Deepmind on Stanford RL Forum</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://97hongjun.github.io/categories/deepmind/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Reinforcement Learning, Bit by Bit</title>
      <link>https://97hongjun.github.io/p/rl-bit-by-bit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://97hongjun.github.io/p/rl-bit-by-bit/</guid>
      <description>Presenter  Xiuyuan (Lucy) Lu
Research Scientist,
DeepMind, Mountain View
Abstract  Reinforcement learning agents have demonstrated remarkable achievements in simulated environments. Data efficiency poses an impediment to carrying this success over to real environments. The design of data-efficient agents calls for a deeper understanding of information acquisition and representation. We develop concepts and establish a regret bound that together offer principled guidance. The bound sheds light on questions of what information to seek, how to seek that information, and what information to retain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lectures on Information Directed Sampling</title>
      <link>https://97hongjun.github.io/p/lec-ids/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://97hongjun.github.io/p/lec-ids/</guid>
      <description>Presenter  Tor Lattimore
Research Scientist,
Deepmind, London
Abstract  Tor will give a whirlwind tour of a series of recent papers on the information directed sampling algorithm for sequential decision-making. The results come in three flavours. First, generalising and applying the IDS algorithm to problems with a rich information structure such as convex bandits and partial monitoring. Second, showing a connection between the optimisation problem solved by IDS and the optimisation problem that determines the asymptotic lower bound for stochastic structured bandit problems.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
